Guide to the Hematopoiesis Research Project, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Hematopoiesis research project, School of Medicine, Yale University, records
1992-2004
RU 975
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
8.75
(7 boxes)
The records consist of data and research notebooks documenting the hematopoiesis research project of Diana Krause, associate professor of laboratory medicine and pathology at the Yale School of Medicine.
Yale University. School of Medicine
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-D (YRG 27-D), Records of committees of the Yale School of Medicine.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale School of Medicine, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of data and research notebooks documenting the hematopoiesis research project of Diana Krause, associate professor of laboratory medicine and pathology at the Yale School of Medicine.
Hematopoiesis; Medicine -- Research; Krause, Diana N.; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Research notes and data of the Hematopoiesis Research Project, 1992-2004; Accession 2005-A-096
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - DSK - Deletion mutants CD34, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - DSK - Antibody (902 and new), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - DSK - Cap site transciption, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brett - EMSA/CD34 fusion protein, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - DSK-Penn RNA notebook (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Si Chin Research Notebook, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Mouse Transplants (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - DSK - mCD34 Immunohistochemistry, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Adro Hsu - Cd34 Regulation 1+2, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 39 - 40)
  - Unidentified binder